

# Aishwarya Patil

Jr. Project Management Executive

ar.patil2793@gmail.com ⊠

7262960606 / 8767901922

Pune O

linkedin.com/in/arpatil93 in

A motivated and creative individual with a penchant for Marketing and Management along with industry experience of more than a year in Project Management and Social Media Marketing. Displayed proficiency in satisfying the customer and business with end to end solution's, problem solving attitude and process optimization via software, data and analytics.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Jr. Project Management Executive**Birlasoft Pvt Ltd

02/2020 - 03/2021

Pune

- Responsibilities
- Provided support in managing projects via compilation of various artifacts such as plans, analyses, and other formal documents.
- Monitored and controlled all processes and aspects related to 102 projects which were part of multiple customers.
- Controlled and avoided risks by discussing with the concerned project managers.
- Reviewed project roles, KPIs, POs, Invoices etc for all projects assigned to me.
- The major task executed by me was of invoice generation for customers like Cummins, Siemens, Autodesk, Lilium, Wabteche etc by end of the month. Total Invoice generation for all projects and customers tallied to ~ 45,026,825 USD.

### Social Media Marketing Intern Bulbandkev

10/2019 - 01/2020

Pune

- Responsibilities
- Managed all the social media channels like Facebook,
  Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram of the company.
- Built and executed a social media strategy using methods like market competition along with audience research and identification.
- Produced content like info graphics, images, posts for all the social media channels of the company for brand awareness and to engage and gain viewership of the audience.
- Generated, edited, published and shared daily content using applications like Facebook creator Studio, Tweet deck - to schedule posts in advance. etc for the company.

#### **SKILLS**



#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Slum Rehabilitation (Graduation project) (01/2017 - 03/2017)

 Understood and implemented a procedure for rehabilitation of an allocated slum area in partnership of the local governing entity

Impact of specialized training on daily wage laborers (PG project) (02/2019 - 03/2019)

 This project was aimed to test the impact of specialized training on daily wage laborers with respect to performance. accuracy, speed etc for the assigned task.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Cooking

Playing with my pet

#### **EDUCATION**

O M.Com

**BMCC** 08/2017 - 06/2019

Pune

Specialization

- Business Administration

**B.Com** MMCC

06/2014 - 06/2017

Pune

Specialization

- Marketing Management